pastrywiz.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of the utmost importance. Our reputation and integrity is directly related to how we serve our clients and customers. Please find below a description of how PastryWiz.com strives to protect the privacy of Internet users, and maintain the Internet as a highly credible medium.

**User Information  
**All users who visit PastryWiz.com retain complete anonymity where PastryWiz.com is concerned. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private properties. PastryWiz.com does, however, collect information which is specific to how you use the Internet. PastryWiz.com servers note details such as the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of analyzing the effectiveness and popularity of PastryWiz.com and to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to keep track of your shopping cart. We will never store any personal information in your shopping cart.

**Registration Forms  
**Our site's voluntary registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or gender). Contact information on the registration forms is collected to e-mail you information about our website. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time.   
Demographic and profile data is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis only.   
**We will never sell or disclose your name, e-mail address, postal address or phone number.**

**Order Forms  
**Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like email address and postal address), and financial information (like credit card numbers). Contact information from the order forms is only used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and to ship the products ordered. Financial information that is collected is used only to bill for products and services ordered. 

**External Links and Public Forums  
**This site contains links to other sites. PastryWiz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**The Cookie Principle  
**PastryWiz.com does currently not use any cookies, but  may do so in the future to keep track of the items in your shopping cart. We will never store any personal information in your shopping cart.

**3rd Party and Advertisers  
**We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. PastryWiz.com has no control over the information collected by third party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third party measurement service where collected information is concerned. If you have questions regarding different third party measurement services and their respective methods of information collection, please contact us.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Disclosure  
**PastryWiz.com openly volunteers its practices of collecting information and it's practices of this site. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please write to us.

Survey

Copyright Š PastryWiz TM
